Timmy Muldoon and the Search for the Shadoweyes Bandit is a
adventure, comedy film directed by Tony Yacenda.
13-year-old Timmy Muldoon's home movie evolves into
the Hollywood film of his dreams.
Timmy Muldoon, played by Owen Teague.
Shadoweyes, played by Cuba Gooding Jr..
Muscle Bruce, played by Jon Bernthal.
Captain McClusky, played by Sean Carrigan.
Veronica Taylor, played by Suzanne Quast.
Officer Bill, played by Dan Perrault.
Kenny Johnson (born July 13, 1963) is an American actor.
He is known for his roles as Detective Curtis Lemansky in The Shield, Butch "Burner" Barnes in Pensacola: Wings of Gold, Detective Ham Dewey in Saving Grace, Herman Kozik in Sons
of Anarchy, Matt Webb in Prime Suspect, Caleb Calhoun in Bates Motel, Dominique Luca in the CBS drama series S.W.A.T., and Tommy Welch on Chicago Fire (2014–2015).
The tone is lighthearted.